{
    "subject": "resource/F._D._Reeve",
    "predicate": "property/shortDescription",
    "object": "Academic, Writer, Poet and Russian Language Translator",
    "human_readable": "F. D. Reeve is an Academic, Writer, Poet and Russian Language Translator.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8260477185249329,
            "question": "Does F. D. Reeve work with the Russian language?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8251621723175049,
            "question": "Is F. D. Reeve known for writing poetry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7897060513496399,
            "question": "What might be the connection between F. D. Reeve's academic and writing pursuits?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7466789484024048,
            "question": "What type of academic work does F. D. Reeve do?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6163597702980042,
            "question": "To what extent does F. D. Reeve's work involve translation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6078522801399231,
            "question": "What are some of F. D. Reeve's professions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6064746975898743,
            "question": "What is the primary focus of F. D. Reeve's academic work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5810596942901611,
            "question": "Can you name some specific works by F. D. Reeve?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5519749522209167,
            "question": "Has F. D. Reeve published any works of poetry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5356906652450562,
            "question": "Besides writing, what other skills does F. D. Reeve possess?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=F. D. Reeve is an Academic, Writer, Poet and Russian Language Translator.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6638_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has F. D. Reeve published any works of poetry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6638_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name some specific works by F. D. Reeve?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6638_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the primary focus of F. D. Reeve's academic work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6638_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6638_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6638_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6638_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6638_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6638_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6638_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6638_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6638_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6638_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6638_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this response is that the documents contain multiple references to F.D. Reeve as an American academic, writer, poet, Russian translator, and editor (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6638/re-ranker-msmarco/4.txt, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6638/re-ranker-msmarco/53.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"F. D. Reeve is an Academic, Writer, Poet and Russian Language Translator.\" Specifically, they mention his roles as an American academic, writer, poet, Russian translator, and editor."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}